jobcrusher.com 2009-02-19

# 

                                   PRIVACY POLICY & YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS
1. How We Protect Your Privacy.
This privacy policy tells you how we collect, use, and protect your personal information at www.JobCrusher.com.
By visiting our website, you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. In particular, you
consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.
2. Minors.
We do not provide services or sell products to children. If you are below the age of 18, you may use our website
only with the permission and active involvement of a parent or legal guardian. If you are a minor, please do not
provide us or other website visitors with any personal information.
3. Policy Is Part Of Our Terms And Conditions Of Use.
Our privacy policy is part of, and subject to, our website's terms and conditions of use. You may view these
terms and conditions by clicking this link.
4. The Type Of Information We Collect From You.
Like most places on the Internet, simply by visiting our website you automatically tell us certain information. This
includes basic information such as your IP address, when you visited, the website from where you came prior to
visiting us, the website where you go when you leave our website, your computer's operating system, and the
type of web browser that you are using. Our website automatically records this basic information about you.
And like many other websites, we may use cookies. In plain English, this means information that our website's
server transfers to your computer. This information can be used to track your session on our website. Cookies
may also be used to customize our website content for you as an individual. If you are using one of the common
Internet web browsers, you can set up your browser to either let you know when you receive a cookie or to deny
cookie access to your computer.
We may also collect any data that you provide us by posting it at our website or by e-mail. You can always
choose not to provide us with information. However, if you do withhold information, we may deny you access to
some or all of our website's services and features.
Some transactions between you and our website may involve payment by credit card, debit card, checks, money
orders, and/or third party online payment services. In such transactions, we will collect information related to the
transaction as part of the course of doing business with you, including your billing address, telephone number,
and other information related to the transaction.
5. What We Do With Your Information.
We use your information to operate our website's business activities. For example, we may use this data to
contact you about changes to our website, new services, or special offers, resolve disputes, troubleshoot issues,
and enforce our website's terms and conditions.
We may, in our sole discretion, provide information about you to law enforcement or other government officials
for purposes of fraud investigations, alleged intellectual property infringement, or any other suspected illegal
activity or matters that may expose us to legal liability.
We may, in our sole discretion, disclose individually identifiable information about you and aggregate data about
our website's visitors (including you) to advertisers or other third parties for marketing, promotional and other
business purposes. By using this website and providing information to us in the process of doing so, you are
expressly agreeing to our collection of such information and disclosure of it to others. If you do not want such
information disclosed to third parties, you should not use this website.
In addition, we may use third party suppliers to provide services on our website. If a supplier wants to collect
information about you, you will not be notified. However, we restrict the way third party suppliers can use your
information. They are not allowed to sell or give your information to others.
6. User Names And Passwords.
Your access to parts of our website may be protected by a user name and a password. Do not give your
password to anyone. If you enter a section of our website that requires a password, you should log out when you
leave. As a safety precaution, you should also close out of your web browser completely and re-open it before

viewing other parts of the Internet.
7. Your Use Of Information And Unsolicited Junk E-Mail.
If you obtain personally identifiable information about another website user, you are not allowed to disclose this
information to anyone else without the consent of the user and our consent too.
We hate junk e-mail (Spam). Information you obtain from our website about us or other site users cannot be
used by you or others to send unsolicited commercial e-mail or to send unsolicited commercial communications
via our website's posting or other communication systems.
8. Your Voluntary Disclosure Of Information To Third Parties Who Are Not Our Suppliers.
You may choose to provide personal information to website visitors or other third parties who are not our
suppliers. Please use caution when doing so. The privacy policies and customs of these third parties determine
what is done with your information.
9. Autoresponders.
We may use autoresponders to communicate with you by e-mail. To protect your privacy, we use a verified opt-in
system for such communications and you can always opt-out of such communications using the links contained
in each autoresponder message. If you have difficulties opting out, you may contact us by sending an e-mail to
support (at) jobcrusher.com (replacing the "(at)" with the "@" symbol and removing the spaces), or sending us
mail to the address listed below.
10. Policy Changes.
The terms of this policy may change from time to time. If such changes are made, we will notify you by a notice
posted on our website's home page of the changes that have been made. If you disagree with the changes that
have been made, please contact us (by e-mail, using a website contact form, or in writing by mail), and any
changes made to this policy will not apply to information we have collected from you prior to making the
changes.
If you are concerned about the topic covered by this policy, you should read it each time before you use our
website. Any questions or concerns about this policy should be brought to our attention by sending an e-mail to
support (at) jobcrusher.com (replacing the "(at)" with the "@" symbol and removing the spaces) and providing us
with information relating to your concern.
You may also mail your concerns to us at the following address:
Job Crusher, LLC
7 Lakeway Centre Court
Suite 202
Lakeway, TX 78734
11. California Privacy Rights.
Effective January 1, 2005, if you are a California resident and our customer, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83 permits
you to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct
marketing purposes. To request this information, please send an e-mail to support (at) jobcrusher.com
(replacing the "(at)" with the "@" symbol and removing the spaces) or write us at the following address:
Job Crusher, LLC
7 Lakeway Centre Court
Suite 202
Lakeway, TX 78734
This policy was last updated on April 10, 2008.
